I Putu Gede Bayu Raditya Pratama

Email: <u>bayuraditya35@gmail.com</u> | phone number: 085706264055 | link linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/i-putu-gede-bayu-raditya-pratama-a265391b8/

PESONAL PROFILE

I was born at September 7, 2002 in Denpasar, Bali. Currently studying at ITB STIKOM BALI since 2020. I am talented in using a computer as a daily tool. I am also a web designer and web developer. I am used to typing fast on the computer. I am a hard worker, disciplined, responsible, polite and good in team work.

EDUCATION

•	SDK Harapan Denpasar	Graduate 2014
•	SMPK 1 Harapan Denpasar	Graduate 2017
•	SMA NEGERI 5 DENPASAR	Graduate 2020
•	INSTITUT TEKNOLOGI DAN BISNIS STIKOM BALI	2020 until present
	S1 - SISTEM INFORMASI	

EXPERIENCE

Mei 2021 – Juni 2021

 Work Training As Data Management Staff Vocational School Graduate Academy Digital Talent Scholarship 2021 at BPSDM Kominfo Yogyakarta

Juli 2021 – Agustus 2021

 Work Training As Junior Mobile Programmer Program Vocational School Graduate Academy Digital Talent Scholarship 2021 at University Gadjah Mada.

January 28, 2021

• Participate in the Applied Microsoft Office Certification Program at Bisma Informatika

SKILLS

WORD | EXCEL | POWER POINT | HTML | CSS | C++ | C | JAVA | SQL | PHP | BOOTSTRAP | Adobe premier pro and After effects | CANVA | Design UI UX figma

Data Management Staff Training				
Roles	Data Management Staff			
Key Skills	Ms Word, Ms Excel, Ms Power Point, web browser, Operation Sistem, Basic Software			
Description	My role in this training is to carry out administrative processes to ensure data is reliable, easily accessible, and up to date in terms of time using ms word, ms excel, and ms power point			
URL Portfolio and certificate	https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1iJnBlCnmsIHofAnitMikicEsOEbAd8uY?usp=s haring			

Applied Microsoft Office Certification Program					
Roles	Applied Microsoft Office Program Participants				
Key Skills	Ms Word, Ms Excel, Ms Power Point				
Description	This program provides opportunities for students / students / workers / individuals who want to get Microsoft Office Certification and are internationally recognized.				
URL certificate	https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1fTYWkAPNnCCMxImW83kjVjbSopMv9UQ F?usp=sharing				

Personal website				
Roles	Web Design (UI UX) dan Front End			
Key Skills	Html, Css, Javasript, Bootstrap and hosting			
Description	This is my personal website which contains my project, brief biography, and contact person			
URL	http://bayuraditya.epizy.com/			

CRUD System – A website that has a feature to create, read, update, delete for student, majors, and lecturers data at ITB STIKOM Bali				
Roles	Web Designer (UI UX), Front End, Back End			
Key Skills	Figma, HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, Bootstrap, PHP My Admin			
Description	This website uses a CRUD system that uses the PHP language and database			
URL	http://sistemcrudstikom.epizy.com/			

Skill sets	Tools
Competence in the area of Office Application	Microsoft word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Power Point, Web Browser
Full Stack Developer	Visual Studio, phpmyadmin, web browser
UI UX DESAIN	Figma: figma.com/@bayuraditya https://www.instagram.com/uix.radit/